# **BRADLEY ROSENFELD**

(224) 650-7624 https://bradleyrosenfeld.com thatguy@bradleyrosenfeld.com

## Overview

I am a developer who is passionate about web development, good design, and information security. I have over 5 years of experience in designing and developing responsive user interfaces for screens of any size. My objective is to work for an organization that is excited about creating secure, user-friendly web applications.

# Education

## **Taylor University**

<a href="http://taylor.edu">http://taylor.edu</a>, August, 2012 - May, 2016<a href="https://bs.science">B.S. Computer Science</a> - New Media / Systems, 3.77/4.0 GPA, Manga Cum Laude

## **Awards**

## **Outstanding Systems Graduate**

Taylor University CS&E Department, 2016

This award is given to a student who best exemplifies what the Systems program is trying to teach through their outstanding class and project work.

#### 1st Place BVU CTF

Buena Vista University, 2015

I competed with a team of students and took first place in an attack/defend CTF competition.

## Skills

#### Languages

- C, C++
- PHP, Python, Ruby, SQL
- HTML, CSS, Sass, LESS, JavaScript

#### **Tools**

- Git, Subversion
- Grunt, Bower, Unix Tools
- Node.js, NPM
- Windows, Linux, Mac OS X

## Libraries & Frameworks

- Ruby on Rails, Express, Flask, Django, WordPress
- Angular.js, jQuery

## Networking

- TCP/IP, DNS, SSH, HTTP, TLS, socket programming
- Apache, Nginx

## **Techniques**

- Penetration testing, reverse engineering
- Debugging, Q/A testing
- Agile, scrum

# Projects

Visit my GitHub profile (<a href="https://github.com/BoringCode">https://github.com/BoringCode</a>) for a list of my open source contributions and projects.

# Experience

## **Sells Group**

https://sellsgroup.com, Web Developer

2013 - 2016

- Responsible for front-end development on client marketing sites. Worked with team to execute project roadmaps.
- Built custom e-commerce platform on top of WordPress. Focused on application security from the front-end to the back-end
- Configured development build pipeline on multiple platforms. Set up automatic production deployments. Configured AWS installations.

### **Floodlight Design**

http://floodlight.design, Web Developer

2011 - 2013

- In charge of front-end development. Converted static Photoshop designs into flexible layouts
- Integrated static templates with WordPress and Joomla templating systems
- Developed JavaScript for site interactions and API integrations

### **Highgate Creative**

http://highgate-creative.com, Mobile Web Developer

2013 - 2014

- · Advised on responsive design best practices. Developed and wrote documentation for an internal responsive web design framework.
- Developed several mobile themes for a custom content management system
- Crafted a jQuery mobile theme for use on a client marketing website